oddschecker.com 2012-11-25

# My Oddschecker | Privacy Policy | Oddschecker

To return to the registration page please click [here](https://secure.oddschecker.com/myoddschecker/register "Register")

Oddschecker is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We use information we collect about you to provide you with the Services contained in our websites located at www.oddschecker.com, www.oddschecker.co.uk and other associated URLs displaying this privacy statement. We appreciate that you do not wish us to circulate your personal details on an indiscriminate basis. This document discloses the privacy practices for Oddschecker including: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected
  * What organisation is collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Under 18s

No one under the age of 18 is permitted to use the Account Opening Service.

### Information We Collect

We only collect personal information in order to provide you with some of our Services. Subject to what is said below regarding cookies, you are free to browse the rest of our Site without information being collected. 

To fully use the Account Opening Service, you will need to register using our online registration form. You will be required to provide us with your contact information (e.g. name, postal address, telephone number and e-mail address). 

Using the Site's web server log files, we use IP addresses to analyse trends, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser and operating system you are using, your IP address etc. 

In addition, we use cookies on certain pages of our site. We may also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. The other type of cookie we use is a 'persistent' cookie. This stays on your hard drive and we use this to automatically identify who you are. The cookie itself contains no personally identifiable information but it does pass an ID to our server which allows us to tie the cookie to your personal information. We do this to allow us to let you know on the homepage what has changed on the site since your last visit. We also use the cookie to track how often you visit the site so we know who our most loyal users are. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you will not be able to use certain features on our site. 

### Our Use of Your Information

We use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customise our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. 

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve any disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular on rare occasions we may evaluate your information to look for users using multiple User IDs or alias. 

We may occasionally send you direct mail about additional services we feel may be of interest to you. This will only come from us and only if you have indicated that you do not object to these offers. 

Your Personal Information is stored in our databases, which are located in the UK. Please note that the information you enter may at some time be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purposes of processing by Oddschecker or any of its affiliates. By submitting your information, you consent to this transfer. 

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

It is necessary to disclose your personal information to the Bookmakers with whom you indicate you would like to open an account. These Bookmakers will then use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. Links are provided to the terms and conditions of use and the privacy policies of these Bookmaker during the account opening procedure. By using the Account Opening Service you consent to such disclosure of you information. 

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. 

As a general proposition, **we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.**

**Advertisers.** We do aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. 

**Legal Requests.** Oddschecker cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. Local, and international law enforcement agents can request and may receive your personally identifiable information. 

### Control of Your Password

If you lose control of the password provided to you during the registration of some of the Services, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

### Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are other members of the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. 

### Security

We use best endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. We use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this. However, you should be aware that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Oddschecker and to the use of that information in accordance with the oddschecker privacy policy. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

You have a legal right to a copy of all personal information about you held by us. You also have a right to correct any errors in that information. 

Please e-mail any questions or comments you have about this policy [click here](http://www.oddschecker.com/feedback "Feedback")

To return to the registration page please click [here](https://secure.oddschecker.com/myoddschecker/register "Register")
